Logan Parker

Loganparker.ca Vancouver, British Columbia

(604) 992-4510 Logandparker4@gmail.com

Profile

Graduated BCom student from the University of British Columbia specializing in Finance and Real Estate with proven technical abilities and problem-solving skills. Exceptional interpersonal and communication skills built on throughout university career. Motivated by a passion for learning and self-improvement.

Education

Bachelor of Commerce, Finance and Real Estate (Honours) University of British Columbia, Vancouver, BC

Completed April 2016

Dean's Honour Roll 2015, 2016.

Work Experience

Investment Analyst, Premise Properties, Vancouver, BC

May 2015—August 2015

- Analyzed all current real estate investments within the company in order to assess current asset performance versus expected performance, reporting directly to the CEO and Founder.
- Underwrote the prospective purchase of a portfolio of residential properties in the Lower Mainland—work I completed was used for finding an equity partner and securing financing.
- Lead the due diligence process on the sale of a commercial property in Vancouver.

Operations Manager, Cowichan Lake Marina, Lake Cowichan, BC (Seasonal) May 2010—August 2014

- Ordered, managed, and sold \$25 000 worth of merchandise per season for the marina's retail store.
- Managed and maintained \$85 000 worth of rental watercraft through scheduling rental bookings, personally performing maintenance servicing, and booking professional servicing when necessary.

Activities and Community Involvement

1st Place, Bentall Kennedy Case Competition, UBC, Vancouver, BC

April 2015

- Performed a market, comparable transactions, and financial analysis to most accurately value one of Bentall Kennedy's properties in the Lower Mainland.
- Created a pro forma to predict investment value for an investor for a five-year holding period.

Vice President & External Public Relations, UBC Ski and Snowboard Club April 2013—March 2015

- Raised \$1 500 for Vancouver Adaptive Snow Sports (VASS) by organizing and executing a skiing and snowboarding contest at UBC with over 400 spectators and 40 contestants.
- Built and maintained a relationship with 28 sponsors throughout the calendar year for the UBC Ski and Snowboard Club—one of UBC's largest student-run clubs.

Skills and Interests

Skills: Adobe Photoshop, Microsoft Office, basic financial application of Python, basic HTML and CSS

Cycling: After graduating from UBC I cycled 3,100 kilometers from Vancouver, BC Interests:

to the border of Mexico at San Diego.

I spent kindergarten to grade five growing up near Santa Cruz, California Surfing:

where I learned to surf and continue to do so on Vancouver Island.

Traveling: I spent the summer following graduation traveling USA and Europe.